Pavel Grigoryev

+375293935377

Linkedin: linkedin.com/feed

Telegram: @PavelGr7

Github: github.com/Pavel-Grigoryev

Email: 3935371@gmail.com

Portfolio: pavel-grigoryev.github.io/portfolio

Minsk, Belarus



Front-end developer

A front-end developer with more than **2 years** of web application development experience. My main technology stack includes **JavaScript** and **TypeScript** programming languages, as well as frameworks and libraries such as **React**, **Next.js** and **Redux**. Experience in creating **SPA/SSR** applications on the **FSD** architecture. Experience in developing websites on various CMS.

Experience

Front-end developer, Online clothing store

May 2022 — present

- I developed additional functionality for the site (modal windows, mega menu, navbar, ajax requests, shopping cart, filtering);
- I fixed bugs on the site and worked on improving the performance of the site;
- I worked with plugins and their adaptation to existing tasks;
- I migrated the online store from the Shopify platform to the Wordpress platform. I customized the Wordpress theme for the developed design;
- I migrated the online store from the Shopify 1.0 platform to the Shopify 2.0 platform. After the completion of the project, the download speed of the mobile version of the site increased from 21% to 68%, and the desktop version from 80% to 94%.

Front-end developer, MTN Haus

November 2021 — April 2022

- I created online stores on the Shopify platform in the frontend development team;
- I adapted extensions for Shopify in new online stores.

Civil engineer, ETM

April 2012 — October 2021

Projects

Dh-designer.com

A multi-page website of a UX/UI designer. The visual design of the site includes two themes: light and dark.

- I developed the site from scratch on a framework **Next.js**;
- I created a scalable application architecture;
- I used the Frames Motion animation library for an attractive visual presentation;
- I set up automatic code verification using **eslint**, **stylelint** and **husky**;
- I configured **Git Actions** and **Docker** to ensure fast delivery of changes to the site.

Stack: Next.js, TypeScript, Zustand, Tailwindcss, Framer Motion, Swiper, Docker, eslint, stylelint.

Memorize App

Memorize is an application for memorizing information using cards.

- I participated in the discussion and creation of the application architecture;
- I've been working with the **REST API**;
- I worked with forms and validation (login, logout, search, data entry);
- I refactored the code, fixed bugs, and optimized performance;
- I created components and pages using **React**.

Stack: React, Redux-toolkit, React-router-dom, Redux-thunk, Axios, TypeScript, MaterialUI, Formik.

<u>Uae-business.com</u>

A news site for the company..

- I created a website from scratch on the Wordpress;
- I worked with the forms, set up the sending of emails;
- I implemented dynamic news uploading to the client side;
- I worked with Figma.

Stack: React, Redux-toolkit, React-router-dom, Redux-thunk, Axios, TypeScript, MaterialUI, Formik.

Skills

JavaScript, Typescript, React, Next.js, Redux, Redux-Toolkit, Zustand, Redux Thunk, Redux-Saga, Rest API, Axois, Formik, React Hook Form, Storybook, Jest test, Snapshot test, Material UI, Ant Design, CSS3, SCSS, Tailwind CSS, HTML5, Git, Docker, Framer Motion, Liquid code, Jira, Figma, Shopify, WordPress, Webflow.

Education

2022 - 2024. IT-INCUBATOR

Front-end developer (React/Redux, TypeScript)

2022. ItGid.info: "JavaScript v2.0" Front-end developer (JavaScript)

2021. FREEMOTE: The Freelance Developer Bootcamp Front-end developer (Shopify, Liquid code, HTML/CSS/JS)

Language

English - intermediate (in progress)
Russian - native

Belarusian - native